Inventory of the Open Society Archives collection
Hoover Institution Archives
Open Society Archives collection
1951-1991
2002C34
Hoover Institution Archives
21 microfilm reels (2.1 linear feet)
Relates to the Polish unit of Radio Free Europe.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2002.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Location of Originals
Originals in: Open Society Archives, Central European University, Prague, Czech Republic
Scope and Content of Collection
Content relates to the Polish unit of Radio Free Europe. Included are critical articles and commentaries against RFE (called attacks or ataki) published on the Polish Radio broadcasts and in the press, as well as reactions (reakcje) and counterattacks in foreign newspapers targeting the state-owned Polish Radio as a propaganda medium of the communist regime.
Radio Free Europe.; Radio broadcasting--Poland.
- Polskie Radio (Polish Radio transcripts), 1951-1959 (pages 1-586) (Reel 1)
- Polskie Radio (Polish radio transcripts), 1952-1957 (pages 1-398) (Reel 1)
- Ataki (attacks in the press), "Dziennik Polski," 1958-1961 (pages 1-192) (Reel 1)
- Ataki, "Dziennik Polski," 1958-1961 (pages 193-1290) (Reel 2)
- Ataki, 1961-1963 (pages 1-82) (Reel 2)
- Ataki, 1961-1963 (pages 83-361) (Reel 3)
- Ataki, 1964 (pages 362-642) (Reel 3)
- Ataki, 1965 (pages 1-333) (Reel 3)
- Ataki, 1966 (pages 334-547) (Reel 3)
- Ataki, 1967 (pages 1-118) (Reel 3)
- Jamming, 1961-1970 (Reel 3)
- Ataki, 1967 (pages 119-870) (Reel 4)
- Ataki, 1968 (pages 1-407) (Reel 4)
- Ataki, 1968 (pages 408-1139) (Reel 5)
- Ataki, 1969 (pages 1-472) (Reel 5)
- Ataki, 1969 (pages 473-867) (Reel 6)
- Ataki, 1970 (pages 1-212, 1-373) (Reel 6)
- Ataki - Reakcje (attacks and reactions), 1971 (pages 1-151) (Reel 6)
- Ataki - Reakcje, 1971 (pages 152-821, 1-531) (Reel 7)
- Ataki - Reakcje, 1971 (pages 532-902) (Reel 8)
- Reakcje, 1971 (pages 903-1082) (Reel 8)
- Ataki - Reakcje (prasa krajowa) 1972 (pages 1-700, 1-439) (Reel 9)
- Ataki - Reakcje (prasa krajowa) 1972 (pages 440-695) (Reel 10)
- Sytuacja finansowa (prasa zagraniczna) 1972 (pages 1-313) (Reel 10)
- Sytuacja finansowa (prasa zagraniczna) 1973 (pages 314-569) (Reel 10)
- Reakcje (prasa krajowa) 1973 (pages 1-303) (Reel 10)
- Reakcje (prasa krajowa) 1974 (pages 304-481) (Reel 10)
- Reakcje (prasa krajowa) 1975 (pages 482-621) (Reel 10)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1974 (pages 1-142) (Reel 10)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1975 (pages 143-345) (Reel 10)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1976 (pages 346-705) (Reel 10)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1977 (pages 1-129) (Reel 10)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1977 (pages 130-499) (Reel 12)
- Prasa krajowa, 1976-1979 (pages 1-661) (Reel 12)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1979-1980 (pages 1-547) (Reel 13)
- Prasa krajowa, 1980-1981 (pages 1-175) (Reel 13)
- Prasa zagraniczna - zamach bombowy, 1980-1981 (pages 1-320) (Reel 13)
- Prasa zagraniczna - zamach bombowy, 1980-1981 (pages 321-619) (Reel 14)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1982 (pages 1-333) (Reel 14)
- Prasa krajowa, 1982 (pages 1-713) (Reel 14)
- Prasa krajowa, 1982 (pages 1-793) (Reel 15)
- Prasa krajowa, 1983 (pages 1-351) (Reel 15)
- Prasa krajowa, 1983 (pages 352-1042) (Reel 16)
- Materialy krajowe, 1984 (pages 1-303) (Reel 16)
- Materialy krajowe, 1984 (pages 304-391) (Reel 17)
- Ataki, 1982 (pages 1-845) (Reel 17)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1985 (pages 1-221) (Reel 17)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1985 (pages 222-287) (Reel 18)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1986 (pages 1-157) (Reel 18)
- Prasa krajowa, 1985 (pages 288-736) (Reel 18)
- Prasa krajowa, 1987 (pages 737-1104) (Reel 18)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1986 (pages 158-209) (Reel 19)
- Prasa krajowa, 1986 (pages 210-637) (Reel 19)
- Materialy polskie, 1988 (pages 1-655) (Reel 19)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1987-1988 (pages 1-268) (Reel 20)
- Prasa zagraniczna, 1989-1990 (pages 269-642) (Reel 20)
- Materialy polskie, 1989-1990 (pages 1-453) (Reel 20)
- Materialy polskie, 1989-1990 (pages 454-529) (Reel 21)
- Materialy polskie, 1988, 1991-1992 (pages 1-792) (Reel 21)